In this video, we're going to test the algorithm that we just wrote.
在这段视频中，我们将测试我们刚才写的算法。
We're going to be counting from zero to N and N as a variable.
我们将从零到N和N作为变量进行计数。
We're going to draw boxes for each of our variables to keep
在我们
track of what value they currently have as we step through our algorithm.
逐步完成算法时，我们将为每个变量绘制方框，以跟踪它们当前的值。
As we begin, N has the value, five.
当我们开始时，N 的值为 5。
The other thing we're going to keep track of is the output of our program.
我们要跟踪的另一件事是程序的输出。
Here is a box labeled, output,
这里有一个标有 “输出” 的方框
and every time we write something down,
，每当我们写下一些东西时，
we're going to write it into this output box.
我们都会把它写到这个输出框中。
Finally, we're going to use a green arrow to keep track of where we are.
最后，我们将使用绿色箭头来跟踪我们的位置。
Right now, the arrow is right before the line that says count from zero to N,
现在，箭头就在显示从零到N计数的行之前，
which means we haven't done this yet. Now, we can start.
这意味着我们还没有这样做。现在，我们可以开始了。
The first thing we want to do is count from zero to N inclusive,
我们要做的第一件事是从零到 N（含）计数，
and call each number that we're counting, i.
然后调用我们正在计数的每个数字，
Since i is a variable,
i。由于 i 是一个变量，
and it's going to start with the value zero,
它将从值零开始，所以
we create a box to hold i and its value of zero.
我们创建一个框来存放 i 和它的值为零。
Now, we enter the next step.
现在，我们进入下一步。
The next thing we're going to do is write down N squared minus two times i.
接下来我们要做的就是写下 N 平方减去两次 i。
We have a little bit of math to do here.
我们这里有一点数学要做。
N is the value, 5,
N 是值 5，
and i has the value, zero,
i 的值为零，
so this gives us 25 minus zero or 25.
所以这给我们 25 减去零或 25。
And again, we're supposed to write this number down,
再说一遍，我们应该把这个数字写下来，
so we place this number into our output box.
所以我们把这个数字放到输出框里。
Now, this process is going to repeat again and again.
现在，这个过程将一次又一次地重复。
Now, i is going to have the value one.
现在，我将拥有价值一。
Once again, we're going to compute N squared minus two times i.
再说一遍，我们将计算 N 平方减去 i 的两倍。
This is the same as last time except i has the value of one.
这与上次相同，只是 i 的值为 1。
This is 25 minus two or 23.
这是 25 减去二或 23。
We write that to our output box.
我们把它写到我们的输出框里。
Now, we just completed i equals zero,
现在，我们刚刚完成 i 等于零，
and i equals one,
i 等于 1
and we're trying to get all the way to i equals five.
，我们正在努力一直到 i 等于 5。
So now, we're working on i with a value of two.
因此，现在，我们正在处理 i，其值为 2。
Once again, N squared minus two times i,
再说一遍，N 平方减去 i 的两次，
which is 25 minus four,
即 25 减去四，
the value is 21, and we will write this to our output box.
值为 21，我们将把它写到我们的输出框中。
Now, we're working on i with the value of three.
现在，我们正在处理值为三的 i。
We're going to write down the number,
我们要在
into our output box.
输出框中写下数字，N 平方减两次 i，25 减去 6，即 19。
And we're going to keep doing this.
而且我们会继续这样做。
For i having the value four, which is 17.
因为我的值为四，也就是17。
For i equals five,
因为 i 等于 5
which is 15. i keeps getting larger each time we step through our algorithm.
，也就是 15。每次我们逐步完成算法时我都会变大。
When i equals 6, however,
但是，当 i 等于 6 时，
we're going to stop because we're only counting up to N equals five.
我们会停下来，因为我们只数到 N 等于五。
At this point, we finished the entire algorithm,
至此，我们完成了整个算法
and the good news is that our answer matches what we were expecting.
，好消息是我们的答案符合我们的预期。
in fact, what we were hoping to produce.
实际上，数字序列就是我们希望产生的。